Christian Franco

Nationality: Spanish Date of birth: 09/06/2001 Phone number: (+34) 626554625

■ Email address: christianfrancosoto@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-franco-soto/

Website: christianfranco.dev

• Home: (Spain)

ABOUT ME

I'm a full-stack developer with a strong focus on back-end and solid knowledge in web development, with 3 years of experience in software development. My passion for programming is combined with a desire to learn and improve my knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

III *Idrica* – Spain

Country: Spain

Full Stack Developer

[08/2023 - Current]

Development of applications and REST APIs with .NET Core (C#) for back-end and Angular (TypeScript) for front-end, using SQL Server and PostgreSQL. Performing development assessment, analyzing requirements, estimating time and resources needed. Use of tools such as GitLab, Postman and Jira in an agile environment.

Ⅲ Técnicas Competitivas S.A. – Spain

Country: Spain

Junior Software Developer

[06/2022 - 08/2023]

- Development and maintenance of a web application for economic management using C# ASP.NET MVC.
- Development, management and maintenance of a database in SQL Server.
- Working group with Scrum methodology.
- Version control with GitLab.
- Use of other tools: NUnit for testing, SonarQube for code quality, DocFX to generate documentation and Jenkins for continuous integration.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Higher Technician in Multi-platform Applications Development

CIFP César Manrique [09/2020 – 06/2022]

Country: Spain

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Spanish
Other language(s): English

SKILLS